Erase House Carter?
Oh my god, I’m gonna die!
You're just a disowned trash-digger!
Who the hell do you think you are?!
Thank Gods Count Carter disowned this freak.
Otherwise, the entire legacy of the Carter family
would have been dragged into the sewer today.
Count Carter has true wisdom.
If this psychotic loser had inherited the title,
House Carter would have fallen by noon tomorrow.
You pathetic fools.
Can't even recognize a real god
standing in front of you.
Oh, a god?
You’re a dirt-eating miner outcast!
What, are you gonna sprout wings and turn into a dragon?
Freak.
You’ll find out soon enough.
Lord Severin.
The lords and federated kings have crossed the swamps.
They're heading to Emeraldstone for your wedding.
Should I send an Report.
No need.
They’re old acquaintances.
As you command.
Whoa, whoa, wait.
Kings and border lords coming to his wedding?
Did I mishear,
or has he completely lost his mind?
You heard it right, Lord Redmond!
He’s gone mad!
Next he’ll claim he’s the Godfather of the Sovereign Sanctum!